

JUNBEOM WOO

Frontend/Backend Developer || EU residence and work permit holder

Dambakken 3, 1, 3460 Birkerød, Denmark

iunbeom2.woo@gmail.com
iunbeom2.woo@gmail.com



+45 44 11 14 18



junbeomwooo

PROFILE INFO

I am 27 years old, I was born in South Korea and I currently reside in Denmark with my partner. I hold a residence permit under the EU regulations, which entitles me to live and work in Denmark. I have a bright and outgoing personality, I consider myself a fast-learner and I am passionate about web development. I have experience in working on projects in teams as well as individualy. I have independently worked on multiple personal projects, one of which integrates MySQL with both backend and frontend development, and showcases my experience in working with modern tech stacks like Next.js. I have a background in visual design and completed a 920 hour coding boot camp. I have improved my English skill through working and traveling in Canada for 6 months.

EDUCATION

Ezen Academy, Full Stack(JavaScript) Web Developer (Front/BackEnd)

August 2022 - January 2023 (920hr / 115days)

Courses

- Front End Programming
- JavaScript Programming
- · Building a Developer Environment
- · Applied Programming
- · Server Programming
- Database
- · Building a Linux Server System
- Bachelor of Visual Design, Jangan University, South Korea

March 2016 - February 2022

Courses

- · Web Design
- · Brand Design
- · Editorial Design · Package Design
- · Advertisement Design
- · Character Design
- · Capstone Design
- · 3D Studio Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service at Seoul Koreansk BBQ, Denmark

November 2024 - Present

Information Desk duties at Lotte Department store, South Korea

October 2020 - February 2021

Customer Service at Cheongnyun Dining and Namu, Canada

November 2019 - April 2020

Customer Service at CJ Food Ville, South Korea

September 2018 - June 2019

HTML & C	ss			
				_
JavaScript	& TypeScı	ript		
React & Ne	ext.js			
Node.js & E				
	xpress			
MySQL				
Git				
Adobe Illus	- 1 2 votovt)h a ta a h a		
Adobe illus	strator α r	— —	- -	_
LANGU	JAGES			
KOREAN				_
ENGLISH				